Guide to the Brigid's Place Records
University of Houston Libraries
Brigid's Place Records
1974-2011
1993-1997
1999-003
Brigid's Place (Houston, Tex.)
9.50 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
Although the Women's Assembly founded Brigid's Place in 1996, the papers in ththe processed portion of this collection span from 1974 to 2011. Some research items date to the late 1980s and early 1990s. The original accession of papers arrived in five boxes, which split naturally into the two categories of the Women's Assembly and Brigid's Place. The papers were arranged topically and chronologically.
Historical Note:
Brigid's Place, the women's center at Christ Church Cathedral, a place of prayer, meditation, research, and mutual support, is dedicated to the spiritual and personal development of women. Brigid's Place was established in 1996 by Christ Church Cathedral's Women's Assembly when the Assembly recognized that it needed to expand both its resources and its space. The Women's Assembly itself was formed in 1993 as a network for progressive women of Christ Church Cathedral.
Originally, the Assembly envisioned Brigid's Place as a separate project, but the Assembly and Brigid's Place soon became closely identified with one another. Brigid's Place assists women in finding mentors, in forming support networks through Small Groups, and in searching for answers to questions about female spirituality, gender roles, theology, and other issues facing religious women in the modern world. Brigid's Place participants join Small Groups, which focus on specific issues of particular importance to women at different stages in life
Brigid's Place is a 501 (c) (3) nonprofit organization with a board of directors; the Rotating Circle, composed of members from smaller communities who serve limited terms, is the advisory board of Brigid's Place. Brigid's Place also publishes an annual newsletter and brochures for their programs.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Brigid's Place (Houston, Tex.); Christ Church Cathedral (Houston, Tex.)
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Correspondence; Minutes; Newsletters; Photographs
Topical Term:
Nonprofit organizations -- Texas -- Houston; Women -- Religious aspects -- Christianity
Acquisition Information:
Donated by Brigid's Place, 1999. Additional materials were acquired in 2011 as part of a donation by Patty Turney. Another accrual, currently unprocessed, arrived November 15, 2013.
Conditions Governing Access:
The processed materials in this collection are open for research. Unprocssed materials from the 2013 accession may be restricted and not available for access. For questions about materials in this collection or to request access, contact curator Vince Lee (velee@uh.edu).
Scope and Contents
Although the Women's Assembly founded Brigid's Place in 1996, the papers in ththe processed portion of this collection span from 1974 to 2011. Some research items date to the late 1980s and early 1990s. The original accession of papers arrived in five boxes, which split naturally into the two categories of the Women's Assembly and Brigid's Place. The papers were arranged topically and chronologically.
The largest portion of the papers concern the Women's Assembly and Brigid's Place, which are the first two series of the collection. Because the activities of the Women's Assembly quickly became synonymous with Brigid's Place, the papers of the Assembly are included with Brigid's Place beginning with 1996, the year of its foundation. Therefore, the papers relating to the Women's Assembly from 1993 through 1995 were placed in the Women's Assembly series. All papers from 1996 on are in the Brigid's Place series; however, researchers may note some overlap with 1996, and should check both series for complete documentation. These two series contain administrative records; agendas, minutes, notes and fliers for the Rotating Circle and Small Groups; the records of activities, speakers, and ministries for both organizations; and publications.
Papers filed throughout the collection, but which did not directly relate to the functioning and activities of either Brigid's Place or the Women's Assembly, are arranged into two more series: Christ Church, and Other Related Information. The Christ Church series contains various newsletters, minutes, and documents relating to the Christ Church Cathedral, and to other organizations associated with the parish. Other Related Information contains information regarding other religious and women's organization not directly tied to Christ Church, as well as various research materials. The current organization is primarily topical by series and sub-series, and is either topical or chronological within the sub-series.
Two additional boxes of materials were acquired in 2013 and have not yet been processed. These are currently described as Series 5, but may later be integrated with other series once processed.
Detailed List of Contents
- Brigid's Place
  Scope and Contents
  Brigid's Place contains the papers relating to the administration and activities of the women's center at Christ Church Cathedral, beginning in January 1996 and continuing through 1999. This series is divided into eight sub-series: Administration, Rotating Circle, Small Groups, Ministries, Activities, Speakers, Labyrinth, and Publications. The Administration sub-series contains the documentation for the creation and organization of Brigid's Place, as well as some financial records, correspondence, and information regarding its board of directors. The folders are arranged alphabetically by subject. The Rotating Circle and the Small Groups sub-series include agendas, minutes, notes, and fliers for the Rotating Circle administrative committee and for the various topical committees of Brigid's Place. The Rotating Circle folders are arranged chronologically, while the Small Groups folders are arranged alphabetically by group name. The Ministries sub-series contains similar information, as well as descriptions and plans for the different outreach programs associated with Brigid's Place. Those folders are arranged chronologically. The Activities and the Speakers sub-series include the plans, budgets, attendance records, fliers, and brochures for various liturgical events, workshops, retreats, and educational lectures sponsored by Brigid's Place. The sub-series are arranged chronologically. Information regarding the research and execution of the Labyrinth, a major project of Brigid's Place in conjunction with other Houston area religious organizations during 1997, is contained in the Labyrinth sub-series. The Publications sub-series contains The Women's Journal newsletter, and Lenten Meditations, a group of prayers for women during the season of Lent.
  - Creation
    - Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Meetings, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Budgets, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Long Range Planning, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Architectural Plans, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Organization
    - Statement of Purpose, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - By-Laws, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Non-profit Status, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Organizational Structure, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board Meetings Information, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Brochures, approximately 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Computer Disks, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1997, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Directors Lists, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Press, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 16a)
    - Donors, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Historic Documents, August 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rotating Circle
    - Board of Directors/Members, 2000-2011 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Meeting Information, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Meeting Information, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Meeting Information, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Information, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Retreat, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Small Groups
    - Feminist Forum, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Noontime Meditation, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Women in the Workplace, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Worship Weavers, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ministries
    - Jail Chaplaincy, February 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Jewish and Christian Women in Conversation, June 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Women in Crisis, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Caring Partners, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Noah Project, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Brigid's Hope, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Family Pathfinders, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34a)
  - Activities
    - Calendars, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Seasonal Programs, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Blessing of Brigid's Place, August 25, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Yoga, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Outdoor Program, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Workshops, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Theater LaB Benefit, April 1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Creative Writing Workshop, Spring 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - "Racism: Woman to Woman", September 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Mary Magdalene Festival, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Mary Magdalene Festival, 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Retreats, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - "Creativity as Sacrament" Workshop, May 8-9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - "A Time for Friends", November 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - St. Brigid's Festival, 1998-2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Women's Spirituality Day, January 23, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Hildegard von Bingen Festival, April 30, 1999; 2004 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Julian of Norwich Festival, May 5, [?] (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - “Search for the Feminine Soul”, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - “Changing Woman, Changing Church”, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - “A Time for Friends”, 1998-2005 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - “President’s Luncheon”, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 10th Anniversary, November 11, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - “Culture, Authority and the Church”, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Faith on Trial, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Speakers
    - Laurence Freeman, May 1996-Nov. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - J. Pittman McGhee, September 6-7, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Richard Howard, September 26, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Living the Questions series, September 1996-April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Jane Chance, September 1996, June 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Don Benjamin and Jennifer Elkins, October 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Anne Carolyn Klein, November 1-2, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Erika Lorentz, December 6-7, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - John Lienhard, 1996, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Martha Serpas, January 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Edith Mayo, January 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Tinka Tarver, March 14-15, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Rev. Michael Mayne, April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Elizabeth Smith, April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Patricia Orr, June 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Sue Monk Kidd, September 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Sue Monk Kidd, Study Questions for The Dance of the Dissident Daughter, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Sue Monk Kidd, Secret Life of Bees, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Fr. Thomas Keating, March 1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sister Helen Prejean, March 6, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Betty Adam, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Jim Cotter, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Carol Christ, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Patty Turney, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Labyrinth
    - Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Budgets, March-April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Events, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Presenter Training, February 9, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Volunteers, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Research, 1991-1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Publications
    - Women's Journal, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Women's Journal, 2000-2011 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Lenten Meditations, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Lenten Meditations, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Gifts From Within, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - “Notes on the ‘F’ Word”, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - The Wholeness Initiative, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Programs, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Brochures, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Women's Assembly
  The sub-series for the Women's Assembly are nearly identical to those of Brigid's Place: Administration, Rotating Circle, Small Groups, Ministries, Activities, Speakers, and Publications. The materials are dated 1993-1996. Because Brigid's Place is an extension of the Women's Assembly, the duplicated sub-series contain the same types of papers that are included in Brigid's Place, and follow the same arrangement.
  - Administration
    - Organizational Meetings, March-June 1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Budget Rationale, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Mission and Goals, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Organizational Chart, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Brochure Plans, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Mailing Lists, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Parish Reports, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 47a)
  - Rotating Circle
    - Meeting Information, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Meeting Information, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Meeting Information, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Publicity Committee, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Small Groups
    - Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Contemplative Woman, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Feminist Forum, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Mothers and Daughters, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Through Her Eyes, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Weavers, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Wisdom Bearers, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Women in the Workplace, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Women on the Cusp, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Women Praying for Women, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Women Saints and Mystics, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Women in Crisis, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ministries
    - New Hope Housing, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Caring Partners, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Activities
    - "Savvy, Spirited, Southern", 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Retreats, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - "Let Freedom Ring", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - St. Lucia Evening, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Facilitator Workshop, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - St. Brigid Festival, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Taskforce (unidentified), 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Personal Empowerment Workshop, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Workshops, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - “Three Gates of the Feminine Soul”, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Speakers
    - Christine Cozzens and Donna Sadler, September 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - "Herstory": Women of the Bible, November 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Carol Anderson, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - East Harris County Convocation, approximately 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - John Lienhard, May 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Parker Palmer, September 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Allison Cheek, May 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Daphne Grimes, April 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Lois Ann Peckham, May 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Publications
    - Newsletters, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Matrix Award, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Notes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Notes, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Photos, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Mailing List, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Christ Church
  The Christ Church sub-series and folders contain papers relating to Christ Church Cathedral and its other organizations for the years 1985 through 1999. The folders in this series are arranged alphabetically by topic: Administration, Cathedral Organizations, Cathedral Bulletin, Events, and Miscellaneous. The Administration folders are arranged alphabetically, and contain church policies, brochures, parish reports and plans of action. The Cathedral Organizations includes minutes, information, and fliers concerning Christ Church organizations other than the Women's Assembly or Brigid's Place. The folders are arranged alphabetically. The two Cathedral Bulletin folders contain an incomplete set of newsletters for the Cathedral from 1992-1999. The Events folder contains fliers for various church functions. The Miscellaneous folders contains fliers, clippings and other information related to Christ Church, but not directly related to the other subseries and folders in the Christ Church series.
  - Administration
    - Brochures, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Building Use Policies, 1997, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Church Policies, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Parish Report, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Plan of Action, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Cathedral Organizations
    - Daughters of the King, 1985-1986, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Guild of the Christ Child, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Ladies' Parish Association, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Mary and Martha Guild, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Women's Breakfast, 1992-1997 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Cathedral Bulletin, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Cathedral Bulletin, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Events, 1994-1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - “A Time and Place for Health and Minds”, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Other Related Information
  The Other Related Information series contains papers not directly related to Christ Church Cathedral, the Women's Assembly, or Brigid's Place, dated 1986 through 1999. Four sub-series are found in the Other Related Information series: Organizations, Conferences/Events, Research, and Printed Materials. The Organizations sub-series folders are arranged into two groups: Women's and Religious. Women's Organizations include both secular and religious groups focusing primarily on women. Religious Organizations include only religious groups that have no particular gender association. The folders in the two Organizations groups are arranged alphabetically. The Conferences/Events sub-series includes programs and information for conferences or similar events that were not sponsored by Christ Church, the Women's Assembly, or Brigid's Place. These folders are arranged alphabetically. The Research sub-series contains clippings, papers, notes, brochures and publications relating to the various issues that concerned the women of Brigid's Place. These folders are arranged alphabetically by topic. All of the material in the Other Related Information series provides context for the different activities, networking, and ideas that influenced the creation and functioning of Brigid's Place. The oversized box contains three issues of New York Times Magazine, January and April 1990, and June 1993; three issues of the Texas Episcopalian, September 1996, and March and May 1999. The box also contains one page from the April 1995 Texas Episcopalian, and ten sheets of butcher paper with notes written on them.
  - Organizations
    - Women's
      - Crisis Pregnancy Center, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Episcopal Women's Caucus, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Federation of Houston Professional Women, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Gladney Center (adoption), undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Greater Houston Women's Foundation, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Houston Area Women's Center, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - National Assembly of Religious Women, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - UH Women's Studies Program, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Women for Social Witness, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Women in Mission and Ministry, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Other, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Searching the Scriptures/The Monday Group, 1997-2007 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Religious
      - Center for Progressive Christianity, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Episcopal Diocese, 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Institute of Religion, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Jung Center, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - "Let Freedom Ring", 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - New York Open Center, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Other, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Conferences/Events
    - "Catching Fire", 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "Continuum of Violence", 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Trinity Institute National Conferences, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "A Vision of Wholeness", 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - "Women in Photography", 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Other, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - “Religion and the Feminist Movement”, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - “Exploring Justice”, May 11, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - “Interfaith Women’s Ramadan Iftar”, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Women United Conference, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 29a)
  - Research
    - Anglican Spirituality and Liturgy, 1974-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Diversity, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Family Issues, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Feminism, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Gospel of John, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Male/Female Difference, 1988, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Prayer, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Reproduction Issues, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - St. Brigid of Ireland, 1954, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - St. Hildegard von Bingen, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - St. Lucia, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Science and Religion, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Supplemental Liturgical Materials, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Women and Education, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Women and Spirituality, 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Women in the Clergy, 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Women's Health, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Women's Self-Esteem, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Other, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Printed Materials
    - Journal of Women’s Ministries, Winter 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mayor’s Summit on Women, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Moorehouse Publishing, Fall 2002 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Sewanee, Fall 1997 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Houston Chronicle, 1997-2000 (Ovs box 5, Item 1)
    - Texas Episcopalian, 1996-2000 (Ovs box 5, Item 2)
    - New York Times Magazine, 1990-1993 (Ovs box 5, Item 3)
    - Mayor’s Summit on Women Framed Art, 1999 (Ovs box 6, Item 1)
    - WNBA Houston Comets Posters, 2001-2002 (Ovs box 6, Item 2-9)
    - Mike Moncrief Photograph, undated (Ovs box 6, Item 10)
    - Ann Richards, undated (Ovs box 6, Item 11)
    - Printed Poem, undated (Ovs box 6, Item 12)
- Unprocessed additions
  This series contains 2 boxes of materials received in 2013. Unprocssed materials may be restricted and not available for access. For questions about materials in this collection or to request access, contact curator Vince Lee (velee@uh.edu).